<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Best Site Ever! (not)</title><link>https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/</link><description>Recent content on The Best Site Ever! (not)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/based/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/based/</guid><description>&lt;p>= Why does everyone based have to be so stupid? =&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
—-&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
This is something I&amp;#39;ve been noticing for a while: You become aware of a person and think they&amp;#39;re normal. That&amp;#39;s the baseline. Then they say or do something extremely impressive. Godly. Based, even. You start to look up to them for that.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
But then you notice it. Often it&amp;#39;s only one, but there&amp;#39;s some part of their life that they&amp;#39;re just completely floundering on. Maybe they know it, maybe they don&amp;#39;t. But it&amp;#39;s there. You know it&amp;#39;s there, and that colors everything you respected about them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;strong>Why does everyone based have to be so stupid?&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
I don&amp;#39;t know either. If you ever find out, let me know.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/idkman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/idkman/</guid><description>&lt;p>I feel sad. I feel mad. I think I shouldn&amp;#39;t bother. I want to fix it all in one fell swoop. I want to find a shortcut. I want to build on what exists. I want to realize it all. I want it I am tired I am lazy. Truly slothful. Just can&amp;#39;t give up. How long, how long will I slide?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
Nothing is wrong. Why not? Why would it be? How are we here, why do we even? Let it go. Let it stay. Be that as it may, I&amp;#39;ll be on my way. Maybe some more money will fix it? Throw some money, burn some cash. Sing to the river. But what if it all returns to nothing? A pillar, a fortress, a lair, leaning and sliding as the ground upon which it is founded shifts manically. A cataclysm. A temptation. An inevitable pull towards chaos. But entropy is just the tendency towards equalization. We can&amp;#39;t have equality. Some are more equal than others. Isn&amp;#39;t that dystopian? Probably less than most of the boomer cargo cult. I beg to dream and differ. Just another paper I&amp;#39;ll never deliver. Amen brother Ben, shot a rooster killed a hen. And then? What then?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
The earth is rotting. Give me a boat that will carry two, and we shall sally forth, the liar and his lie. I&amp;#39;m worse off all the time. But time is relative. But Light is absolute. Nah, can&amp;#39;t be. Light is relative and all perception is based off it so we measure it consistently with itself all the time unless relative scales come into play, and even then that is just the illusion of making sense. Particles, waves, what does it profit a man to gain the whole world and lose his life? Quit my pain and end the strife. But no. I must live, must go on in this crazy world, must type out insufficient ramblings on an insecure and fraught platform. Stacking up papers, drinking away my money (on Mtn Dew of course– let no one call me an alcoholic), picking glass out of my shoes. A shattered mirror wall, destined to fall, a crash in the night.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
Last night I had a dream. Several details have already slipped away but I&amp;#39;ll relate what I recall of it here:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
It was some anime. At least, a bunch of the people looked like anime characters. There was a magic system based on &lt;strong>can&amp;#39;t remember the name&lt;/strong> but it contained three tiers that were red and circular. Like Lisp parentheticals (`()`). I went to the arctic entry of Eagle River Walmart and I was Kirito from SAO Abridged. there was some sexual-like but definitely-not-sex sexuality to the magic system. As I entered I turned left and right there was a minor hostage situation. Both participants were girls, one was Asuna (again, the Abridged version of course). She yelled something about there being no plot and I retorted, &amp;#34;come on, sure there&amp;#39;s a plot. It&amp;#39;s not that bad a show.&amp;#34; then I took off into the store. There was a very-realistic-metal-but-not-real gun involved and I was in a chase around the empty aisles in the store. The only employee was the mamasan from KFC and she was telling us to be more composed in the store. I asked if it was about the fake-but-realistic gun and she said no but took it anyway. That part ended, I went back to the mandatory Japanese shrine hot springs house with the babbling brook containing a visualization of the magic system, and began waking up. Then I finished waking up, stumbled out of my room, and found the broken mirrors.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
What&amp;#39;s the truth? What&amp;#39;s a lie? Is everything a rip-off of Overlord? Is Overlord a rip-off of SAO? All I know is, SAO is not an isekai. It&amp;#39;s not an isekai. It is anything but an isekai. It is the same as anything silly and bad. Bad? Yeah sure I guess it&amp;#39;s bad. But hey, I guess I&amp;#39;ll have to continue on my way. Bye.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/selflangs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/selflangs/</guid><description>&lt;p>= Communication is fake, actually =
—-
Surely you&amp;#39;ve noticed it by now. People know and use different definitions of relatively common words in English. I don&amp;#39;t know how it is outside of English, I&amp;#39;m not there. All I know is, this approaches absurdity.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
Now, the evolution of language is a known thing. A thing so widely known as to be tiresome. And, as an extension of this, we have on the inner layer of culture slang, and on the outer layer loan-words.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
But now in the age of the Internet, slang moves faster than ever. In fact, I would go so far as to say that its current trajectory can be likened to a snowball rolling down a mountain: innocuous, but inexorably accelerating till it hits the ground.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
What&amp;#39;s the ground? Babel. Total loss of mutual intellegibility. The older generations will maintain a fairly well-rooted dialect while their children and grandchildren sail far and away with a much smaller and more nuanced vocabulary.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
—-&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
This is not the problem I came here to talk about. It&amp;#39;s just a fun look ahead (or in the mirror?) that lies tangent to the real issue:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;">Every single person&lt;/span> speaks a different language.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
Here&amp;#39;s some arguments, for those who are into it.&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The logical argument from thought:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>All humans over the course of their development arrive at a unique cycle of thought&lt;/li>
&lt;li>All verbal/linguistic expression is derived directly from thought&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Thus, all verbal/linguistic expression is the product of a unique cycle of thought.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>that, my friend, is either a perfect syllogism or a cheap definitional cop-out. If your language distinguishes between those. Mine does but only when it&amp;#39;s applied to something I disagree with.&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>All misunderstandings are caused by different points of view&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Different points of view are…&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Ack screw it this is just drawing an obvious conclusion that was foregone from the first line. sorry to waste your time.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol></description></item><item><title/><link>https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/tutorials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/tutorials/</guid><description>
&lt;div id="outline-container-headline-1" class="outline-2">
&lt;h2 id="headline-1">
Sub-sub-index of tutorials
&lt;/h2>
&lt;div id="outline-text-headline-1" class="outline-text-2">
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>[.] TODO: all below:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li class="checked">&lt;a href="https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/tutorials/scraping/">using sed and curl to extract information from webpages&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li class="unchecked">all the things I do with `nvim`&lt;/li>
&lt;li class="unchecked">how to pick a laptop (from a &lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;">connoiseur&lt;/span>)&lt;/li>
&lt;li class="unchecked">remembering facts and information without trying&lt;/li>
&lt;li class="unchecked">why I don&amp;#39;t use `grep` anymore&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Deletion</title><link>https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/deletion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mitchmarq42.xyz/articles/deletion/</guid><description>
&lt;div id="outline-container-headline-1" class="outline-2">
&lt;h2 id="headline-1">
This is a meme
&lt;/h2>
&lt;div id="outline-text-headline-1" class="outline-text-2">
&lt;p>I&amp;#39;m not actually deleting anything in particular&lt;/p>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div></description></item></channel></rss>